let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: " Which equality does <b> Universal Adult Franchise</b> come under?",
    answer: "Political Equality",
    options: [
      "Political Equality",
      "Economic Equality",
      "Social Equality",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "A political party that is usually recognised in four or more states by the Election Commision is Known as _________?",
    answer: "National Party",
    options: [
      "General Party",
      "Regional Party",
      "National Party",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "When two or more parties come together to form the goverment then, that is Known as ___________?",
    answer: "Coalition Goverment",
    options: [
      "Coalition Goverment",
      "State Goverment",
      "National Goverment",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which Country was the first country to adopt democracy as a <b> Goverment </b>?",
    answer: "Greece",
    options: [
      "India",
      "France",
      "Greece",
      "USA"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "A type of Democracy where all the people came together in one place to make important decisions and frame laws directly is Known as _________?",
    answer: "Direct Democracy",
    options: [
      "National Democracy",
      "Direct Democracy",
      "Indirect Democracy",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },

 {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The number of seats in the Vidhan Sabha of Madhya Pradesh ___________?",
    answer: "230",
    options: [
      "200",
      "250",
      "230",
      "280"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Elections which are held every <b> Five Years </b> is Known as __________.",
    answer: "General Elections",
    options: [
      "General Elections",
      "By-Elections",
      "Mid-Term Elections",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is not an example of <b> Regional Party</b>?",
    answer: "Bharatiya Janta Party",
    options: [
      "Akali Dal",
      "Shiv Sena",
      "Bharatiya Janta Party",
      "Dravida Munnetra Kazhagam"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In which Article <b> Is the pratice of Untouchability a Punishible Offence?",
    answer: "Article 17",
    options: [
      "Article 19",
      "Article 17",
      "Article 15",
      "Article 21"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following word does not defines <b> Dignity </b>",
    answer: "Honest",
    options: [
      "Honest",
      "Worthy",
      "Honoured",
      "Respected"
    ]
  },



];